

💌 FrostBDonovan@gmail.com | 🧥 fdonovan98.github.io/portfolio | 🖸 FDonovan98 | 🛆 frostdonovan | 🛅 frost-donovan

Summary.

I am a passionate Producer with a background in programming, with a strong knowledge of version control using Git, agile methodology, and an excitement for facing new, interesting challenges. I have lead teams which have published to both Itch and Steam, always with a focus on maintaining healthy and flexible working practices. I have been using my time post graduation to recover from burnout, as well as expanding my knowledge of Art Production. My ideal position would be an Associate Producer role, with a strong focus on growing my skills and experience to progress to a more senior position.

Skills

- · Agile Management: User Stories, Story Points, Velocity, Sprint & Release Planning & Review, Scrum, CD Pipelines
- Software: Jira, Confluence, Git, Trello, GitHub & Bitbucket, Google & Microsoft Suite
- · Art Software: Blender, Substance Painter, Clip Studio Paint
- Languages: C#, C++, Latex, Github Actions
- Game Engines: Unity, Unreal Engine 4

Published Games ___

Castan - Producer

Unity 2020.3

SELF PUBLISHED TO STEAM (HTTPS://STORE.STEAMPOWERED.COM/APP/1836170/CASTAN/)

September 2021 - May 2022

- · Utilised Story Points & Velocity, Release Planning, and Jira to manage scope
- Facilitated & assisted with several significant redesigns
- · Developed a Github Action workflow to automatically build, test & publish daily builds to Steam

Carma - Producer

Unity 2019.4

- SELF PUBLISHED TO STEAM (HTTPS://STORE.STEAMPOWERED.COM/APP/1603990/CARMA/)
- · Worked with a multidisciplinary team to bring Carma from concept to published game
- Planned sprints and development milestones using Agile

· Shortlisted for the Grads In Games Student Game Award

- Removed blockers and streamlined development pipelines
- Focused on maintaining team health and reinforcing healthy working practices
- Set up Steam store and maintained updated builds

Published June 2021

Awards

Finalist, Grads In Games Student Game Award

Education

Falmouth University BSC COMPUTING FOR GAMES

Falmouth, United Kingdom

Sept. 2019 - June 2022

· Worked with multi-discipline teams to bring several games through a full development cycle

- · Published two to Steam, one of which was shortlisted for Grads In Games Student Game Award
- · Wrote a dissertation on Continuous Delivery (CD) In Student Teams, implementing and analysing the effect of CD pipelines
- Graduated with a 2:1 Honours

Work Experience _____

GLASS NOMAD GAMES

Director

FXPLUS

Falmouth, Cornwall

March 2021 - Current

June 2020 - September 2021

- Started a company to publish video games my team and I were developing
- · Managed company accounts and government-required paperwork
- Handled Steam registration, set up, and backend work for multiple titles

Senior Ambassador

Falmouth, Cornwall

• Responsible for the smooth running of events

- Managed the distribution of Student Ambassadors during events
- · Relied on to handle any complications or problems that arose during an event

FROST DONOVAN · RÉSUMÉ JULY 26, 2022